{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the highest level in the object model?",
      "correctAnswer": "BasicObject",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "Object",
        "PrimitiveObject"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which core object includes the Kernel module?",
      "correctAnswer": "Object",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "BasicObject",
        "PopcornObject"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Does String include the Enumerable module?",
      "correctAnswer": "No",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "Yes"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What happens when a value becomes too big for Fixnum?",
      "correctAnswer": "It is automatically converted to a Bignum.",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "It turns into a Float",
        "It automatically truncates"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "In what order are the values of a hash iterated?",
      "correctAnswer": "The order in which they were inserted.",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "The order of their size",
        "The order of the keys"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are two uses of ranges?",
      "correctAnswer": "comparison and iteration",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "collection and comparision",
        "iteration and collection"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is not a use of the splat operator?",
      "correctAnswer": "Product of two arrays",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "Explode or expand the elements of an array.",
        "Collect arguments of a parameter list into an array."
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Does a while block define a new scope?",
      "correctAnswer": "No",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "Yes"
      ]
      
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the case statement in Ruby have fall-through behavior?",
      "correctAnswer": "No",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "Yes"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the meaning of self?",
      "correctAnswer": "The current object.",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "The user's conscience",
        "The current context"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does a bang (or exclamation point) at the end of a method signify?",
      "correctAnswer": "A mutation on the receiver object",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "A loud operation",
        "Ruby is excited to execute the method"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "When might you explicitly use the return statement?",
      "correctAnswer": "To return from a method prematurely",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "When the Ruby gets bored of executing",
        "When the method causes a stack overflow"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a singleton method?",
      "correctAnswer": "A method that is available only on a single object",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "A method that wants to be alone",
        "A method that can be executed only once"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a factory method?",
      "correctAnswer": "An initialization method that creates specialized instances of a class.",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "A method that is created by the Ruby Environment",
        "A method that was born in the Industrial Revolution Era"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an IO object?",
      "correctAnswer": "An object that can be used for file data transfer.",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "An object that can be used for bulk data deletion",
        "There's no such thing"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "If more than one version of a Gem is installed, which version will be used?",
      "correctAnswer": "The Gem with the highest version number.",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "The Gem that was installed first",
        "Neither, Ruby hates merge conflicts just as much as you do"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What error is raised if a method is passed the wrong number of arguments?",
      "correctAnswer": "ArgumentError",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "IOError",
        "404 Error"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What error is raised if method name resolution fails?",
      "correctAnswer": "NoMethodError",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "YesMethodError",
        "MaybeMethodError"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the difference between \"puts\" and \"print\"?",
      "correctAnswer": "puts appends a newline character to the output",
      "tags": ["Ruby"],
      "wrongAnswer": [
        "puts is more efficient",
        "Ruby likes puts more than print"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
